Kevin Maguire

Full-Stack Developer

CONTACT INFO

Home Base:
Northampton, MA

Telephone & Email:
603-867-6827
k.w.maguire.ii@gmail.com

LinkedIn & GitHub:
Linkedin.com/in/
kevin-maguire-ii
Github.com/KWMprojects

TECHNOLOGY

Languages:

* * * * Python

* * * * JavaScript/
ES6

Tools:

* * * Django

* * * VSCode



Version Control:

Database:
* * PostgreSQL

About:

As a student at Code Platoon, I'm learning to be a full-stack developer and plan to bring my acquired skills to my new career in tech: my military experience emphasized teamwork, communication and perseverance; and working fulltime as a 911 EMT increased my problem solving, emotional intelligence and resilience. I'm new to the tech industry and ready to go all-in.

Experience:

Code Platoon *Full-Stack Web Developer Bootcamp*

Jan 2020 – Apr. 2020 *Chicago, IL*

Education:

University of New Hampshire Bachelor of Science: Biomedical Science Fall 2016 Durham, NH

Employment:

Charter Communication

Field Technician

Feb. 2019 – Jan. 2020 *Worcester, MA*

- Excelled in customer service and maintained a 5/5 customer satisfaction rating for several months
- Repaired and troubleshooted telecommunication systems and company equipment, resulting in a second lowest repeat call ranking for consecutive months
- Consistently rated within the top 40% of employees on all metrics
- Performed residential installations of telecommunication networks

American Ambulance Services

Emergency Medical Technician

Oct. 2014 – Nov. 2018 Somersworth, NH

- · Obtained primary 911 EMT after eight months of employment
- · Assessed nature and extent of illness or injury to establish and prioritize medical procedures
- Observed, recorded, and reported patient condition or injury, treatment provided, drug and treatment reactions in post-run patient report to be utilized by hospital staff
- · Administered first-aid treatment and life-support care to sick or injured persons in prehospital setting

United States Army and NH National Guard

Officer Candidate & Signal Support Systems Specialist

Nov. 2011 – Present Concord, NH

- Responsible for all encryption and communication security
- · Training manager for communication and IT systems
- Supervisor for junior enlisted teams from 5 to 20 soldiers
- Responsible for equipment valued in excess of \$400,000

Projects:

Rummi-Klub

Web application for playing Rummikub with friends and family. Rummi-Klub provides a fun and interactive way to bring the family together while social distancing is a priority. Technologies used: React, Node.js and boardgame.io.

https://rummiklub.netlify.com/

Job Search Application

Web application aimed at finding a new career and staying updated on the latest news. The career and job search use Adzuna and NewsAPI API on a Django Rest Framework backend with a React frontend. Users have full CRUD functionality to save, view and delete user-reliant career and news posts. https://github.com/KWMprojects/jobsearchapp_frontend